

## 

Hello, I'm Eahea Ratan, a passionate FrontEnd Software Developer. I am an expert on making web applications based on HTML, CSS, and Javascript. I love to do most of the things using javascript and its lib/frameworks like reactjs, nextjs, nodejs. I love to do complex and logical things more that make me happy. want to make the web easy for all.



irashad42@gmail.com



kandapara, jalsi 1350, dhamrai, dhaka, bangladesh.



github.com/iamrashed01



01933431058



facebook.com/eahea.ratan

# EAHEA RATAN

FRONTEND SOFTWARE DEVELOPER



**EDUCATIONS** 

2013 - Feb, 2017

Diploma in computer engineering SAIC INSTITUTE OF MANAGEMENT &

TECHNOLOGY (SIMT)



### **SKILLS**

- React Js
- NextJs
- Typescript
- Typescript
- TailwindCss
- MaterialUI
- NodeJS
- MongoDB
- ExpressJs



### **LANGUAGES**

- Javascript
- Html
- Css

- Python
- C

# O

### **EXPERIENCES**

Feb, 2022 - Present (9 months +)

NexusLab

### FRONTEND SOFTWARE ENGINEER

- Created frontend web applications for top clients of crypto market.
- Learn of things like Typescript, Socket, Web3 and many more..

May, 2018 - Sep, 2021 (3 years 5 months)

ItechSoftSolutions

#### SENIOR FRONTEND SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

- Created frontend web applications for top clients and Envato marketplace.
- manage/lead to the Frontend team.
- Learn of things like ReactJs, NextJs, NodeJs and many more..

May, 2017 - Nov, 2017 (7 months)

ByteCode - Digital Marketing Firm

### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

 it was an small company and i joined as junior frontend developer, i learn many things from seniors, everyone was so friendly and helpfull minded.